

ALDI ALFIANDI

Website Developer, IT Support Specialist, UI/UX Designer, Website Programming Tutor Male | He/Him | 23 years old | 27 August 2000 | Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia. aldialfiandi2708@gmail.com | +62-857-9863-8002 | https://abaddon-x.github.io

PROFILE

Summary

I have been experienced in Web Programming since 2019. I can talk in both English and Indonesian language moderately. I have a great desire to seek new experiences and learn new things with a clear purpose. I always have a sheer of will to put all the loyalty, integrity, effort, and dedication in order to achieving goals.

EXPERIENCE

Woongjin Compass Publishing

March 2023 - Present (Currently Working)
Staff of IT Support Specialist (Remote/WFA)
Working max. 40 hour(s) per week and max. 8 hour(s) per day
Contracted for 1 year with salary of \$350 per month
Supporting sales and digital marketing team on IT related matters

KelasCoding (Self-Employment)

September 2022 - Present (Currently Working)
Web Programming Course Tutor (Remote/WFA)
Working 2 day(s) per week and max. 6 hour(s) per day
Average monthly fee about Rp. 150.000,00 per participant
Teaching about Web Programming and IT related matters

ABADDON-X (Self-Employment)

August 2019 - Present (Currently Working)
Freelance Full-stack Web Programmer (Remote/WFA)
Average monthly earning(s) about Rp. 1.500.000,00 to Rp. 4.000.000,00 per project Building a website of company profile, landing page, personal portfolio, etc.

Dinas Komunikasi dan Informatika (DISKOMINFO) Kota Sukabumi

April 2018 - August 2018
Office Administrator Intern
Handling office administration related matters

EDUCATION

SMK Islam Penguji Kota Sukabumi

Vocational School Year of 2016 to 2019 (Graduated) Software Engineer

EXPERTISE

Soft Skills

Communicative, adaptive, creative, innovative, negotiative, persuasive, influencive, observative, leadership, teamworking, time managing, problem solving, critical thinking, agile working, scrum working

Hard Skills

HTML5, CSS3, PHP, SQL, JavaScript, Java, Git, Linux, Microsoft Office, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Access, PDF Scan/Converting